

💌 molcaytercanli@gmail.com | 🎢 www.tercanli.com | 🖸 molcay | 😾 molcay | 📓 molcay | 🛅 molcay | 🐚 molcay

Summary_

I'm a Software Engineer mostly focused on Python at EPAM Systems Poland. I have 5+ years of experience specialising in full-stack web development, and I have experience with different cloud providers like Amazon Web Services (AWS) and Google Cloud Platform (GCP). I love *nix based environments and enjoy customising all of the development cycles and automating stuff. Also, I am interested in devising better problem-solving methods for challenging tasks and learning new technologies.

Skills

Programming Python, JavaScript, Java, Scala

Web Django, Vue.js, React, Play, Flask, Spring Others Linux, Docker, GCP, AWS, Bash, Jenkins

Languages Turkish, English

Work Experience __

EPAM System Kraków, POLAND

SOFTWARE ENGINEER November 2021 - Present

Worked for an HR and Workforce Management Solution company

• Contributed to a team develops a chatbot for the companies various products

Tech stack: aiohttp (Python), Socket.io for Python (WebSocket), Docker

• Contributed a team develops a tool to manage HR tasks

Tech stack: Django (Python), Docker

Urla Digital Agriculture

Urla, İzmir, TURKEY

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

June 2020 - October 2021

 Developed software and the hybrid infrastructure for IoT devices (Raspberry Pi) that automate the controlled-environment agriculture Tech stack: Python, Docker, Amazon Web Services (like Lambda, RDS, SQS, SNS, DynamoDB, CloudWatch, S3, SES, Timestream, Kinesis Fire-

• Developed a dashboard to configure, update, and control IoT devices (Raspberry Pi) remotely

Tech stack: Django (Python), MySQL, SQLite, Docker

Urla, İzmir, TURKEY Linovi

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

December 2017 - June 2020

- · Developed and maintained web services that serve as chatbots (Jira, Asana, GitHub, Zendesk, Salesforce, Pagerduty) for Google Chat. Tech stack: Play (Scala), React (Javascript), MySQL, Redis, Jenkins, Google Cloud Platform (like AppEngine, Compute Engine, Cloud Pub/Sub, Stackdriver)
- Developed a dashboard for an autonomous driving software company

Tech stack: Vert.x (Java), React (JavaScript), Amazon Web Services

· Contributed a Software as a Service called Asena for an information security firm

Tech stack: Spring (Java), Angular.js (JavaScript), Flask (Python), Redmine

Education & Certificates

EDUCATION

Muğla Sıtkı Koçman University

Muğla, TURKEY

COMPUTER ENGINEERING GPA: 3.52 / 4.00

September 2012 - June 2017

CERTIFICATES

2017, Jan CCNA R&S: Routing and Switching Essentials, Cisco Networking Academy

2016, Jan CCNA R&S: Introduction to Networks, Cisco Networking Academy

2015, Dec Introduction to Cybersecurity, Cisco Networking Academy

FEBRUARY 2, 2023 OLCAY TERCANLI · RÉSUMÉ